You know we should all do.
Go see a musical.
Sure.
And you know which one we should see?
The 1996 Tony Award winner.
Do you happen to know the name of that one?
I don't know, um, Greece.
No.
Rent?
Yes,
rent.
Okay, so when do you want to go?
What?
Oh, I'm sorry I can't, I'm busy.
Hey,
man, it is so hard to shop for girls.
Yes, it is.
At office max.
What did you get her?
A pen.
It's two gifts in one.
It's a pen.
That's also a clock.
You can't give her that.
Why not? Because she's not 11.
And it's not the seventh night of Hanukkah.
What?
What he means by that is,
while this is a very nice gift,
maybe it's just not something a boyfriend gives?
Sure it is.
She needs a pen for work.
She's writing.
She turns it over.
Whoa! It's time for my date with Joey.
All right, look,
look, what did you get for Angela Dumback?
What did you get for her? She didn't have a birthday while we were going out.
For three years.
Look,
it's too late.
And I got an audition.
I can't shop anymore.
I will go out and I will try to find something for her, okay?
Thanks, man.
And oh,
while you're at it,
could you get her a card?
Would you like me to write her a little poem as well?
Or just get a card that has a poem already in it?
Yep.